The New Xbox One Experience brings together
the games, friends, and features you use most.
Sign in by moving left, and selecting your profile.
Then press “B” to close the sign-in area.
Front and center is the latest game you played or app you used,
and as you scroll down
you’ll see your recently played games and apps,
and then your games and apps collection and your pins.
Your recently played games give you links straight to the game hub,
where you can get updates on the game directly from the game developer
and the Xbox Live community.
You can also see which friends are currently playing the game,
and jump to your game clips and screenshots.
Here’s a controller shortcut.
Use your right trigger to jump straight down to your games and apps
and your left trigger to jump back up.
Down the left side is the guide.
Scroll left to open the guide and quickly access your Friends list,
where you can view their current and recent activity.
Below Friends is Parties,
where you can manage your current party or invite friends to a new one.
The guide also has your messages
notifications,
settings,
and snap.
Up at the top is the sign-in area,
where you can get to your Profile
and find all your achievements.
Here’s another controller shortcut:
open the guide from anywhere, even while you’re playing a game,
by double-tapping the Xbox button.
That way you don’t have to stop or even minimize your game
to send party invites and messages.
To the right of Home is the new Community area.
Check out your Activity Feed for the latest updates
and interact with the Xbox Live community by liking,
commenting on, and sharing your favorite content.
There’s lot more to discover, like being able to play your Xbox 360 games on your Xbox One,
and OneGuide, your single destination for browsing TV, movies, and video apps.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.